[
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "6250645ce12f6dec240bdfad",
        "correctAnswer": "Smokin' in the Boys Room",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Me And Mrs. Jones",
            "Mickey",
            "Don't Wanna Fall in Love"
        ],
        "question": "Brownsville Station had a one hit wonder in 1973 with which song?",
        "tags": [
            "songs",
            "one_hit_wonders",
            "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950481",
        "correctAnswer": "syphilis",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life",
            "a dissimilarity of parts often attributable to a difference in origin",
            "the effect of evolution on ethology"
        ],
        "question": "What is Syphilology the study of?",
        "tags": [
            "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Food & Drink",
        "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502e5",
        "correctAnswer": "ApricotÂ ",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Raspberry",
            "Orange",
            "Banana"
        ],
        "question": "Laetrile is associated with the which fruit?",
        "tags": [
            "food",
            "chemistry",
            "food_and_drink"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951010",
        "correctAnswer": "Flea",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Tick",
            "Rat",
            "Dust Mite"
        ],
        "question": "What type of animal is pulex irritants?",
        "tags": [
            "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "id": "6243349bcfaae40c12961454",
        "correctAnswer": "A Hembra",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A Nanny",
            "A Jenny",
            "A Leopardess"
        ],
        "question": "A female llama is known as what?",
        "tags": [
            "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f56",
        "correctAnswer": "Isaac Asimov",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Ursula K. Le Guin",
            "Philip K. Dick",
            "Stephen King"
        ],
        "question": "Which author wrote 'Lucky Starr series'?",
        "tags": [
            "science_fiction",
            "literature",
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95102c",
        "correctAnswer": "Talus",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Tibia",
            "Fibia",
            "Metatarsal"
        ],
        "question": "What is the second largest bone in the foot?",
        "tags": [
            "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950317",
        "correctAnswer": "Lenin",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Marx",
            "Stalin",
            "Gorbachev"
        ],
        "question": "Who was the ruler of the USSR from 1917-22?",
        "tags": [
            "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c18",
        "correctAnswer": "Mexico",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Russia",
            "China",
            "Australia"
        ],
        "question": "From Which Country Does The Poinsettia Plant Originate",
        "tags": [
            "plants",
            "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9513b0",
        "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Fault in Our Stars",
            "Ship of Fools",
            "War and Peace"
        ],
        "question": "In which book does 'Elizabeth Bennet' appear?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    }
]